Hello everyone! This is Haruka Koizumi, aka Oharu!
Hi! So today
Haruka Koizumi's guess video!
Okay, so...
Well, the best guess video ever!
There are so many guess goods!
Haha, why!
Ha-ha-ha!
Um, the tee shirt.
Including this one I'm wearing now.
I have one, two, three
I have a hoodie.
And the interior.
And this one you can't see because of the angle of view.
You can't see it because of the angle of the picture, but there's also an axter
And some birthday goods...
I don't know...
Why does this guy have the most
Why does he have the most guessed goods?
Today
Haruka Koizumi talks about
Haruka Koizumi's guess video
I didn't do this voluntarily.
I received a request from a fan
Thankfully, I received it, so...I was so grateful to receive this.
Well, what do you all think
Haruka Koizumi's guesses
I'd like to talk about what you think of Haruka Koizumi today!
So, please take a look at it until the end!
Please take a look!
Let's start!
ED]
Yes, so, we have asked for your guess videos, well, we have asked for your guess points, so thank you very much for your requests, and thankfully, the guess videos of the other 5 members have received 10,000 views, and we really love the 5 specially selected members. I really love the five specially selected members and the six members, so I am very grateful for that,
I'm really grateful for that, but I've received many kind words from many of you asking me to do a "Hello Guess Video", so I'd like to do it.
I couldn't stop taking pictures of them. I felt that they really love me. Thank you very much.
Okay, I will now introduce the recruitment video. Well, in many ways, you have a mentality of steel, I can't read the kanji. You have a strong mentality. Thank you very much. Mental strength. Is that your guess? I'm glad.
Well, she sometimes comes off as a very heavy woman, lol. Is that a point of recommendation, too? Thank you very much.
I love my laugh so much. It makes me very happy. Thank you very much. What is this, a video to express gratitude? Is that it?
Thank you for your singing, your laughter, your voice, everything. Thank you very much.
I like that you are surprisingly folksy. I'm glad. I'm glad. I am a commoner. Thank you.
He has a broad perspective. They see all around. I am glad. Thank you very much. I can see every corner of the room because everyone is in every corner.
Surprisingly, you look good in cute outfits. Surprisingly what? Thank you very much. I'm glad I look good in cute outfits. Yay!
I'm wearing a HEATTECH today.
Simply cute. Thank you very much. The battery is dead.
Yes, the battery is charged and I will continue.
Is this a push point? I don't know what a push point is anymore.
I'm glad you call yourself Haru. I like to call myself Haru.
What's this? I'm practicing a little bit.
I love the gap between the cool way you sing and the cute way you laugh during live performances.I love the gap between the cool singing and the cute smiling during the live.
Thank you for the part where she smiles with her big mouth open!
I'm glad to see your expression both when you're singing and when you're not singing.
I'm a little conscious of my facial expressions when I'm singing, so even when I'm not singing I'm very happy to hear your compliments, thank you.
The exchange on Instagram between you and the chairman of the board is very interesting.
I'm so glad you're so good at putting it all together, mc.
Thank you for the great job of putting together the mc, and thank you for the pink.
I'm glad you look good in pink.
headgear
It goes with food?
Ha-ha-ha.
I got a new one recently.
I got a new one.
New one.
I'll show you.
Where's the new one?
What's that?
Oh, there's the new one right there.
I got a new one.
Famous.
Thank you.
Yes, thank you for the most adorable place in the whole universe.
Thank you for that video. Okay? All right, guys.Thank you very much for this video. Okay? Hey guys!
I bet Oharu is most into cool songs like standards and July Cider.
Really? Thank you very much.
I think everyone has their own unique charm. I will do my best.
If you see Oharu on Youtube, you will definitely want to buy her a drink. He has a gag game. I'm really saying that ? You guys don't laugh too much for that. Thank you very much.
Her personality is funny without being a girlie-girlie, which makes her a real treat for people of the same sex. Really? Thank you. I'm glad.
You're a family man. I'm glad. Thank you. You're very family oriented.
The part where you say, "Ha-nee". Thank you. Huh? What's this? Thank you.
Favorite food. The way he looks like he's about to say "strawberries" and eats ramen with gusto. I love it. Thank you. I'm glad.
I like ramen and recently, Hidakaya's bomb stir-fry.
The way you tell us that you love us. I love you. Thank you.
When you make a joke by yourself and make a comment by yourself. Thank you. Thank you. I'm glad.
You have an excellent memory. Thank you. I get compliments on my memory. I also get compliments from the members. Thank you.
This is embarrassing.
Thank you for where the concert is.
How can you sing with such a strong voice from such a thin body?
I'm so happy.
I'm so happy. I think I'll stop now.
I'm getting a little embarrassed.
Love songs and "Get's Haru's Fake" are the best!
I'm glad I haven't sung the fake song lately
I haven't done any live shows, so I haven't done any fake songs I want to do fake songs again
When I was having a hard time studying for the exams, listening to Haruka's song made me want to work harder
Thank you.
Thank you very much.Thank you, that's nice of you.
I've been on social networking sites for 4 years and I'm a good friend to other people.
I'm like a diplomat of Tokisen. Thank you very much.
I like your unpretentiousness. Thank you.
I don't decorate.
I want to be born as a childhood friend with the girl I love.
I like the way you play "I want to be born as a childhood friend of yours".
Thank you. I want to be born as a childhood friend with you.
I think it's like we've been friends since we were kids and we're going to be friends
I like the way she sings so well and powerfully.
I can feel how much you love your fans. Thank you very much.
I love it when you laugh. Thank you.
You look so cool at live performances. Thank you.
He carries 2 liters of water.
I like the way you work so hard and sincerely in everything you do.
Thank you for being so happy to be here.
Thank you.
Thank you for the way you talk so happily, it makes me happy too.
Thank you for never forgetting to thank the members, the staff, and the advertising staff for all their hard work.
Thank you for never forgetting to thank everyone involved, including the members, the staff, and the publicity department Thank you for the outbursts of love you show from time to time
When you say you want to be a Mandrian when you are born again... please!
Thank you for being born again Oharu-san, I'll stay this way even if I'm born again
Thank you for being so funny. Thank you for being so good at putting emotion into your songs.
Thank you.Thank you.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I don't know...
I don't know.
You're so busy.
I don't know...
something
What's going on?
Thank you very much. I can't stand it!
I'm crying so hard over my video.
Thank you so much for your love!
The one where I'm wearing a Baymax headband and crying...
Thank you so much!
I'm so glad I did my best.
I'm really thankful that you guys are here.
I haven't used it at all, so I'll just leave it here for now.
Come on, Panko. It's cold, isn't it? Come here.
I was so confused about the angle.
I was so confused about the angle. It's not in the picture at all.
He's really busy. He's really busy.
I'm really busy. I'm sorry, it's not on.
I'll do it later. Thank you. Thank you so much.
I can't do it anymore.I can't do it anymore
I can't do it anymore I'm crying now I can't do it anymore
You sing so well, your interpretation of the lyrics is so expressive, your voice is so moving, thank you.
You're so natural and cute, but sometimes you're so vivid that you're in charge of pink in Tokishin.
When you're in Tokishin, you learn to be a little bit more mature.
Especially from red and yellow people. So I'm a little bit thankful to Tokishin members.
Smile. Thank you.
Anyway, you learn reactions very quickly, even though we've only talked a few times.
I've loved Oharu ever since she looked into my eyes and waved to me.
That was beautiful, thank you.
You fully understand the anxiety of the fans about the group's growth, and you say things to dispel that anxiety.
You prove it not only with your words but also with your appearance in the live performance. Thank you!
Thank you for the big sneeze. Thank you.
Thank you.
You're a good singer, you're cool, thank you.
Ponytail looks good on you!
Your sad expression is genius. Thank you.
I'm glad you're friendly. Thank you. I'm friendly.
You've got a tongue!
He's too much in love with "Propaganda V".
It's all written down here.
You're so nice to the group.
I'm so happy.
He has an amazing memory. He remembers the faces and names of fans and what we've talked about.You have an amazing memory, you remember the faces and names of your fans, you remember what we've talked about.
YouTube appearances, tickers, narration, each one cute, each one fun and cute, I love the sense of entertainment, thank you.
You're so expressive with your emotions, both when you're singing and when you're not.
You have great style. Thank you. I'm so happy.
You work hard
She eats a lot. Thank you.
The gap between her serious face when she sings and her normal face. Her smile is so cute. And she's a good comedian. Thank you.
The members and staffs love your advertisements.
He's a bit of an old man inside.
The gap between him and me was so big that it scared me at first.
I have a good friend who makes my youtube thumbnails and dragonfly gifs.
Thank you for being my best friend who makes youtube thumbnails, dragonfly gifs, etc.
I know this is a bit off topic, but I've been feeling a lot of kindness from people lately.
I've had a lot of friends who have been very kind to me, like telling me they'll make time for me because they're busy, or when I have to go out after work, some of my friends have even stayed a little bit earlier to wait for me.
Or when I'm busy, and they're not that busy, but because I'm busy, they want to go somewhere I want to go.
My family and friends have all been so kind to me, and so many of them.
Like everyone else, the other day, the other day, I'm filming right now, after the screening in Makuhari, and I've had two screenings in Makuhari.
I visited Osaka and Tokyo for two days at the screening in Makuhari, and there were people who came all the way to Osaka to see me.
There were people who came to Osaka to see me, there were people who waited for me in Osaka, and there were people who came from Osaka to Tokyo to see me.
I think there are a lot of people who come to see me because they follow my guess, and of course there are a lot of people who come to see me even if they don't guess me.
I think there are a lot of people who spend a lot of time on me, on everyone else, and on us, so I'd like to thank you all for your time.
I am so grateful that there are so many people who give their time to us, and I really appreciate it.
Thank you for the part where you eat the food so deliciously, for managing your facial expressions so well, and for the sad faces when you say "I'm sure it's a standard" and "I'm sure it's an absolute must".
You're easy to relate to and you look like a crybaby.
I'm so glad you're a fan of Tokiyo, and I'm so glad that you're not just a fan of them, but a fan of Tokiyo yourself.I'm glad to hear that Oharu is a fan of Tokiyo herself, beyond being a fan of the fans, thank you very much I'm a fan of Tokiyo, I really think they are a very cute and charming group.
Yes, I like your voice, your singing voice and usually your voice when you are talking is very attractive, thank you so much for this.
Thank you for your friendliness.
Thank you for going out of your way to pick up any comments from the members, I'll do my best
I think Hachitaro is a genius of long tones, and he's a genius for sakkii, and he's cute, too.
Oharu-chan, thank you for the way you love cute girls even though they are cute, and thank you for always treating your fans like friends.
I love the way you try so hard when you sing... thank you for your hard work... and I love that you have a lot of service spirit.
Thank you for your facial expressions at the bureau, I don't know what it was.
Thank you for making me want to work harder, too. Thank you for the way your facial expressions change during the intro at the end of the song "Selfish Princess".
Thank you for the ponytail and the half up-do.
Thank you for always liking my photos.
Thank you for always liking my photos, and I'll like them as much as you like.
I'm glad that you like my stories, and I'm glad that you like each other's stories, and I'm glad that you like each other's stories, and I'm glad that you like each other's stories.
I'm also really happy that my main fans or other fans are so close to each other and take pictures with other main fans.
I really want to stay in touch with them when they take pictures of me with their friends.
I'm grateful that everyone gets along so well with me, and of course I'm also very happy when people come to the site by themselves.
I'm also grateful for those who come to the site by themselves, but I also really like it when everyone gets along with each other.
I'm really happy. Thank you. I'm a little clumsy.
I know I'm clumsy, I know I'm clumsy, I know I'm clumsy, I know I'm clumsy.
Thank you for your comments on mc, your blog, your sns, your talks, your concerts, your fans, etc.
Thank you for your ability to catch my attention, and I love the way you flap your hands while singing the chorus after the rain.
Thank you for your ability to draw my attention to you and your fans at the concert.
The ecology of the ecology is in a strange place
Thank you for your cute looks, your strong voice, and your smile that makes me see your white teeth. Thank you for your positivity, I'm glad to be your friend.
I'd like to be your friend and I'm glad you're so positive thank youI love the way she looks like an idol, but she's shy when she says cute lines.
I love Haru-chan's mature expression in Star's mv.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
Thank you for looking after each and every one of us, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
ah thank you thank you thank you for the compliment thank you thank you I love the way you laugh, it's so dynamic thank you thank you you you really make me think we're friends, it's so intimate
Thank you for the same cute angle in the selfie.
Thank you for your strong face, for the gap between your daily life and the live performance, for your singing ability beyond my imagination and for the way you make me laugh even though your face is so cute.
I'm really sorry that I can't introduce you all, but I've received so many compliments and I'd like to thank all of you for your kind words.
I'm really sorry that I couldn't introduce all of them, but I've received so many comments, and one of the advertisers wrote me a lot of comments about what he liked about me, which really made me realize that I'm here thanks to everyone's support.
I think that what I can do is to enjoy this idol activity as much as I can and do my best.
I'm really happy that everyone is feeling this way, but I think the most important thing I can do right now is to give everyone lots of love and to express my gratitude to them.
I'm very happy that so many people have come to like me and my humanity.
I will continue to enjoy myself and do my best in my own way.
If you liked this video, please click the "Good" button and subscribe to our channel.
This guess video is really like a thank you video for the members of the promotion department, so if you like me and the members of the promotion department, please give me a good button.
If you like me and if you love the members of the advertising department, please click the Good Button and I will do the same.
I'd like to end with a little insert of the goods I've worked so hard to put together.
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel.